Sparks Photographs
undated
- Photographs, 1860-1997
  - Woman working on a painting with umbrellas around her, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1583; 2 1/4 x 1 3/4 (Box 6)
    Photograph of two unknown women. One them is facing the camera holding an umbrella over a painting while the second woman is facing away from the camera and focused on the painting. No identification.
  - Two men leaning on a picket fence, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1584; Mounted photograhic print; 2 x 1 5/8 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Photograph of two unidentified men standing on the opposite side of a picket fence from the cameraman. There is a large tent behind the fence with a stove coming out of it. Inscripted on the front: Pocket Kodak.
  - Unidentified man under a tree, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1585; Mounted photographic print; 2 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Photograph of an unidentified young man wearing a suit with a long tie. He is visible in profile. There is a tree and a yard with a fence in the background behind him.
  - Unidentified boy, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1586; Mounted photographic print; 2 x 3 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Small portrait of an unidentified young man wearing a suit and tie. No identification.
  - Unidentified woman, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1587; Mounted photographic print; 1 7/8 x 3 7/8 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Photograph of an unidentified woman. She is wearing a dress with a lacey veil or shawl over her hair and covering her shoulders.
  - Unidentified woman, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1588; Carte de visite; 2 1/4 x 3 3/4 (Box 6)
    Carte de visite of an unidentified woman wearing a dress with an apron and a ruffled collar. There is an apron around her waist and she is standing next to a short square pillar covered with a cloth.
  - Unidentified young man in a suit, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1589; Cabinet card; 4 1/4 x 6 1/2 (Box 9)
    Cabinet card of an unidentified young man dressed in a suit with a watch chain and a medal on his lapel. He is standing next to a wicker lawn chair.
  - Unidentified man in a suit, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1590; Cabinet card; 4 1/4 x 6 1/2 (Box 9)
    Cabinet card of an unidentified man wearing a suit with a white bowtie and watch chain. He is standing with his arms behind his back. Cabinet card was prepared by Riverside Studios.
  - Unidentified baby, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1591; Carte de visite; 2 1/2 x 4 (Box 6)
    Carte de visite of an unidentified baby sitting in a dress. Carte de visite was prepared by W. H. Masters.
  - Unidentified girl, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1592; Carte de visite; 2 1/2 x 4 1/8 (Box 6)
    Carte de visite of an unidentified young girl wearing a light colored dress with a dark, fur-lined jacket over it. She is resting her arms on a cushion. Photographer: W. W. Sawyer.
  - Unidentified man with a polka dot tie, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1593; Cabinet card; 4 1/4 x 6 1/2 (Box 9)
    Cabinet card of an unidentified man wearing a suit with a polka dot tie. He is posed so that the right side of his face is visible. Cabinet card prepared by Riverside Studios.
  - Unidentified boy and baby, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1594; Mounted photographic print; 1 7/8 x 1 3/8 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Photograph made of two images. The image on the left is of a baby in a white garment. The image on the right is the same baby being held by a young boy wearing a suit sitting in a chair. No identification.
  - Wedekind mine, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1595; Albument print; 5 x 4 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Albumen print of buildings at the Wedekind mine, located east of Reno. A sign on one of the buildings reads "G. M. Sparks General Merchandise." Handwritten on verso: Wedekind Mine.
  - Two women standing at a fence, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1596; Albumen print; 2 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Albumen print of two women wearing dresses and looking past a fence. They are standing next to a bush. No identification.
  - Woman sitting on a hill, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1597; Albumen print; 2 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Albumen print of an unidentified woman sitting on the side of a hill. She is wearing a dress.
  - Unidentified young man, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1598; Photographic print; 1 1/4 x 3 3/8 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Partial photograph of an unidentified boy standing in a field. He is wearing a checkered jacket.
  - Four boys, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1599; Albumen print; 1 3/4 x 1 3/8 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Albumen print of four unidentified young men wearing suits. Two are standing and two are sitting. The man on the bottom left is smiling goofily.
  - Unidentified woman, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1600; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 1 3/4 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Photograph of an unidentified woman wearing a headscarf and dress suit. Behind her is a dog running in a field.
  - Four dogs, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1601; Albumen print; 4 7/8 x 4 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Albumen print of four dogs, three standing and one laying down by a house. The smallest dog is interacting with the dog laying down. The dogs possibly belong to the Sparks family. Handwritten on verso: The family dogs.
  - Woman sitting in a motorcar, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1602; Albumen print; 3 1/4 x 5 1/4 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Albumen print of a young woman sitting confidently behind the wheel of a motorcar. There are trees in the background. No identification.
  - Herd of sheep next to a fence, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1603; Albumen print; 5 x 4 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Albumen print of a herd of sheep next to a fence. In another pasture is a herd of cattle.
  - Yosemite National Park, circa 1940; UNRS-P2017-13_1604; Photographic print; 4 5/8 x 2 7/8 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Photograph of a landscape of Yosemite National Park which has Half Dome visible on the right side of the image. Photograph developed by Bear Photo Service on September 5, 1940.
  - Half Dome at Yosemite National Park, circa 1940; UNRS-P2017-13_1605; Photographic print; 2 7/8 x 4 5/8 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Photograph of a landscape of Yosemite National Park in which Half Dome is visible. Photograph developed by Bear Photo Service on September 5, 1940.
  - Square tower, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1606; Photographic print; 2 1/2 x 4 1/4 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Photograph of a tower with mountains in the background.
  - Boy and girl in front of a barn, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1607; Photographic print; 5 3/8 x 3 3/8 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Photograph of a boy and girl standing next to a beam in a farm yard. Behind them is a barn and a fence. No identification.
  - Woman sitting in a chair, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1608; Albumen print; 3 3/8 x 5 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Albumen print of an unidentified woman sitting in a wooden chair writing a note on the arm of the chair. There is a drink on the other arm of the chair. She appears to be sitting on a covered porch.
  - Boy and cowboy with dogs, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1609; Albumen print; 5 x 4 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Albumen print of a man on horseback next to a boy and two dogs. The man is holding some kind of sack in his hand. No identification.
  - Four men in front of a Christmas tree, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1610; Albumen print; 5 x 4 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Albumen print of four men sitting in front of a Christmas tree in a living room. The light from the window behind the tree is silhouetting the men, making identification difficult.
  - Herd of cattle in a field, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1611; Photographic print; 4 5/8 x 3 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Photograph of a herd of cattle in a field. There is sagebrush surrounding the field.
  - Hunting party with some bears strung up, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1612; Photographic print; 3 7/8 x 3 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Photograph of a group of men and dogs posing for a picture next to a tree. There are some bears strung up from trees. Possibly a part of a Sparks hunting party.
  - Two story house, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1613; Albumen print; 5 x 3 7/8 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Albumen print of a two story house with a fence in front of it.
  - Man driving a wagon drawn by two horses, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1614; Albumen print; 5 x 4 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Albumen print of a covered buggy being drawn by two horses and driven by an unidentified man.
  - Man and woman fishing at a stream, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1615; Albumen print; 5 x 4 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Albumen print of an unidentified man and woman standing near a river. The man is holding a fishing pole over the river and the woman is watching him.
  - Fireplace with a mounted bison head, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1616; Photographic print; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Photograph of a fireplace in a home. Above the fireplace are six flower vases. There is a bison head trophy mounted above the fireplace.
  - Four women playing golf, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1617; Photographic print; 5 1/2 x 3 3/8 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Photograph of four women standing on a golfing green holding golf clubs. They are wearing bowler hats and looking at the camera. No identification.
  - Unidentified woman sitting on a fence, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1618; Photographic print; 3 1/8 x 7 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Photograph of an unidentified woman sitting on the edge of a fence in a corral. She is wearing a long trench coat and a hat.
  - Man with a stack of sacks, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1619; Photographic print; 3 1/4 x 3 3/8 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Photograph of an unidentified man bending over to inspect a bag in a stack of bags. Behind him is a carriage being drawn by four horses and full of people.
  - Waterway between buildings, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1620; Cyanotype print; 2 x 1 3/8 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of a waterway with some three story buildings in the background. Along the right side of the waterway is a pier-like structure.
    "Photograph was stored in an envelope with a branded cow and the following written on the outside: John Sparks, Cattle and Horse Grower, Cheyenne, Wyoming. Ranges - Lodge Pole and Pawnee Creeks, and Brown Creek, north of North Platte River. The photograph has been removed and resleeved. Print is being stored in an envelope with other small albumen and cyanotype prints from this collection. "
  - Wall with a flag on top, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1621; Cyanotype print; 2 1/4 x 1 5/8 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of a person in front of a wall with a flag at the top. No identification.
    "Photograph was stored in an envelope with a branded cow and the following written on the outside: John Sparks, Cattle and Horse Grower, Cheyenne, Wyoming. Ranges - Lodge Pole and Pawnee Creeks, and Brown Creek, north of North Platte River. The photograph has been removed and resleeved. Print is being stored in an envelope with other small albumen and cyanotype prints from this collection.
  - Large two story building, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1622; Cyanotype print; 2 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of a large, two story stone building which looks like a palace.
  - Two houses, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1623; Cyanotype print; 2 x 1 3/8 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of two houses in the countryside.
  - Balcony view of a small town, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1624; Cyanotype print; 2 3/8 x 2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of a balcony view of a small town. In the middle ground is a horse drawn wagon and in the foreground are some plants.
    This print is a duplicate of 01678.
  - Women carrying buckets through a shopping square, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1625; Cyanotype print; 2 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of three maids carrying baskets and walking along a city street. They are almost at an intersection where there is a police man standing facing away from them.
  - City street with shops, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1626; Cyanotype print; 1 3/4 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of a city street with town houses and shops lining the street. There are a couple of boys walking along in the street.
  - Two boys standing in front of a restaurant, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1627; Cyanotype print; 2 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of two boys standing in front of a building which is labeled "Restaurant." The boys are wearing jackets, pants, and caps.
  - People riding horses down a street, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1628; Cyanotype print; 2 x 1 7/8 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of a people on horses riding down a street. One of them is a woman wearing a white dress and hat.
  - Woman standing on a beach, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1629; Cyanotype print; 2 x 1 5/8 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of an unidentified woman wearing a dark colored dress with white lace at her throat. She is also wearing a cap. In the background is what looks like a beach.
  - Three women under a tree, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1630; Cyanotype print; 2 x 1 3/8 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of three women wearing dresses and hats under the shade of a tree. There is a closed umbrella to the right of the women. No identification.
  - City square in front of a large building, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1631; Cyanotype print; 2 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of a large street with what looks like a cathedral or palace in the background. In the foreground there is a lower paved section of the city.
  - Base of a statue, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1632; Cyanotype print; 2 1/8 x 2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of the base of a statue. Behind the statue base is a walkway lined with trees.
  - A woman named Sarah, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1633; Cyanotype print; 2 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of a woman standing on the beach wearing a dark colored dress with a white collar. Behind her is a pier extending in to the water. Handwritten on verso: Sarah.
  - Three boys in a city lane, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1634; Cyanotype print; 1 7/8 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of three boys wearing suits and caps standing in the street. Behind them on the left is a two story house with chimneys. On the right is what appears to be the side of a warehouse.
  - Group of boys, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1635; Cyanotype print; 2 1/8 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of a group of eight boys wearing jackets and caps standing for a picture. Behind them is a brick building with chimneys on top, a tree, and a fence. No identification.
  - Lane running through the trees, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1636; Cyanotype print; 2 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of a tree lined road leading to some houses. The image is slightly out of focus.
    Photographs 01637 and 01675 are duplicates of this image.
  - Lane running through the trees, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1637; Cyanotype print; 2 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Photograph 01636 and 01675 are duplicates of this image.
  - Two story house with a lake and a field, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1638; Cyanotype print; 2 1/8 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of a two story house with a small lake and field in front of the house. There are trees on either side of the house.
  - Flowering plant, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1639; Cyanotype print; 2 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of some plants and flowers in a yard. There appear to be some daffodils visible.
    Print 01639 and 01688 are mirror images of each other if flipped horizontally.
  - Two girls in front of a bush, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1640; Cyanotype print; 2 1/4 x 1 7/8 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of two unidentified girls standing under a tree. There are bushes behind them. One of the girls appears to be holding a basket.
  - Woman holding a dog, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1641; Cyanotype print; 2 3/8 x 2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of an unidentified woman (possibly a Comstock) holding a small dog while standing in front of a house. Handwritten on verso: Comstock dog.
  - Man in front of a building, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1642; Cyanotype print; 2 1/4 x 1 3/4 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of a man in a suit standing next to a stone building. He is resting his hand on a metal handle.
  - Photo of trees, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1643; Cyanotype print; 2 1/4 x 2 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of trees with the sun shining through them. The print is too dark to determine anything else.
  - Two girls sitting near a beach, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1644; Cyanotype print; 1 7/8 x 1 7/8 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of two girls sitting near a beach. Both are wearing dresses and white caps, with the girl on the left wearing a solid white shirt while the girl on the right is wearing a striped shirt.
  - Woman sitting in a chair in a living room, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1645; Cyanotype print; 2 3/8 x 1 3/4 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of a woman sitting in a chair reading in the living room. She has a dark blanket around her shoulders. No identification.
  - Houses along a street, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1646; Cyanotype print; 2 x 1 3/8 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of some two story buildings along a street. On the side of one of the buildings is the word "Rome." There are some bushes in front of the buildings.
  - Girls wearing maid caps and dresses, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1647; Cyanotype print; 2 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotypes of young women standing in a group wearing dresses and white maid caps standing outside. In the background are a couple wooden sheds. No identification.
  - Man walking towards a building, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1648; Cyanotype print; 2 1/8 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of an elderly man walking into a building. In the background appears to be a church of some point.
  - Woman and boy in a street, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1649; Cyanotype print; 2 x 1 3/8 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of a woman wearing a dress and a maid's cap. She is holding a little boy. In the background, a man is walking along a path. No identification.
  - Three women and a boy outside of a house, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1650; Cyanotype print; 2 1/4 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of three women and one boy standing in the backyard of a house. There are bushes and a path going around the side of the house in the background. No identification.
  - City plaza with people walking through, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1651; Cyanotype print; 2 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of a woman carrying baskets through a plaza in a city. There are some other people also walking through the plaza. No identification.
  - Two women in maid caps shielding their eyes from the sun, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1652; Cyanotype print; 1 5/8 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of two women in dresses and maid caps looking at the camera. They are shielding their eyes from the sun. There are wooden buildingsi n the background. No identification.
    This image is a cropped version of photograph 01652_c2.
  - Woman shoveling snow, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1653; Cyanotype print; 2 3/8 x 1 3/4 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of a woman shoveling a pathway in snow. She is wearing a dark-colored dress and a cap. There are trees in the background. No identification.
  - Group of boys and girls, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1654; Cyanotype print; 1 7/8 x 1 3/8 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of a group of boys and girls in uniforms standing in front of the camera. There is a brick building with bushes at the end in the background. No identification.
  - Alleyway, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1655; Cyanotype print; 2 1/4 x 1 3/4 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of an alleyway between two buildings. At the end of the alleyway is a street with more buildings on the opposite side.
  - Back of a woman’s head, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1656; Cyanotype print; 1 7/8 x 1 7/8 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of the back of an unidentified woman's head. Her hair has been done up in a bun. In the background is a bush.
    "Photograph was stored in an envelope with a branded cow and the following written on the outside: John Sparks, Cattle and Horse Grower, Cheyenne, Wyoming. Ranges - Lodge Pole and Pawnee Creeks, and Brown Creek, north of North Platte River. The photograph has been removed and resleeved. Print is being stored in a microfilm box with other small albumen and cyanotype prints from this collection. "
  - Castle with a wall surrounding it, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1657; Cyanotype print; 2 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of a castle with a wall and fields surrounding it.
    "Photograph was stored in an envelope with a branded cow and the following written on the outside: John Sparks, Cattle and Horse Grower, Cheyenne, Wyoming. Ranges - Lodge Pole and Pawnee Creeks, and Brown Creek, north of North Platte River. The photograph has been removed and resleeved. Print is being stored in a microfilm box with other small albumen and cyanotype prints from this collection."
  - Town houses near a park, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1658; Cyanotype print; 1 7/8 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of some town houses near a small park in a city.
  - Man and woman on horseback, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1659; Cyanotype print; 2 1/2 x 1 7/8 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of a man and woman sitting on horses next to a building. There is a boy running by. No identification.
  - Man next to a tree in a field, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1660; Cyanotype print; 2 1/4 x 2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of a man standing in a field next to a tree. No identification.
  - Woman holding hands with a girl, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1661; Cyanotype print; 2 1/2 x 1 3/4 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cyanotype of a woman holding the hand of a young girl in a backyard. There is a small tree and a patio behind the couch. The woman is holding a dark dress an the young dress is wearing a light colored dress with a hat. Handwritten on verso: Mrs Comstock little girl. No identification.
  - Balcony view of a road and some buildings, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1662; Albumen print; 2 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Albumen print of a view from a balcony showing a road, some buildings, and bushes/plants in the photo.
  - Woman sitting with a paintbrush looking at a painting, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1663; Albumen print; 2 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Albumen print of a woman sitting on a box with her hands close to her chin holding a paintbrush. She is looking at a painting on an easel. Handwritten on verso: Portrait of her father. No identification.
  - Man, woman, and a child walking in a street, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1664; Albumen print; 2 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Albumen print of a man, woman, and child walking along a street in a city. No identification.
  - Man in uniform on a ship deck, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1665; Albumen print; 2 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Albumen print of a man wearing a uniform standing on what looks like the deck of a ship. He has one hand in his pocket and the other on his head. No identification.
    The print is faded and a duplicate of 01670
  - Girl sitting outside, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1666; Albumen print; 1 3/4 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Albumen print of a girl sitting outside. She is wearing a light colored shirt and her hair in two braids. There are trees in the background. No identification.
  - Girl surrounded by bushes, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1667; Albumen print; 2 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Albumen print of a girl standing on a path surrounded by bushes. No identification.
  - Two women standing by a road, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1668; Albumen print; 2 x 1 5/8 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Albumen print of two women standing on a sidewalk by a street. There is a tree in the background. No identification.
  - Curved slopes, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1669; Albumen print; 2 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Albumen of two curved slopes with people standing nearby. No identification.
  - Man in uniform on a ship deck, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1670; Albumen print; 2 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    This print is faded and a duplicate of photograph 01665.
  - Wall with a stone pillar at the end, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1671; Albumen print; 2 x 1 1/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)